Guide to the Eastmont Human Services Center records 1960-2003
Montana Historical Society Research Center
- Correspondence
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 19)
  - Overtime-Part-time Schedules, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 20)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual Updates, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 21)
  - Rathbun, Mary, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 22)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 23)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1995 (Box-folder 22 / 24)
  - Resident Information sent to Daphne Crosbie, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 1)
  - Residential Services, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 2)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 3)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 4)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 5)
  - Swap, Pamela, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 6)
  - Taylor, Loretta, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 7)
  - Virts, Rob, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 8)
  - Walter, Douglas A., 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 9)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1995 (Box-folder 23 / 10)
  - Anderson, Bob, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 11)
  - Austby, Julie, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 12)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 13)
  - Barthel, Gerry, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 14)
  - Berg, Sara, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 15)
  - Contract Professionals, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 16)
  - Department of Corrections and Human Services, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 17)
  - Department of Health and Human Services (DPHHS) Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 18)
  - Blouke, Peter S. (Dr.), 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 19)
  - Dixon, Virgil, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 20)
  - Dolan, Tom, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 21)
  - Mathews, Joe, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 22)
  - Eggum, Marlys, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 23)
  - Haggerty, Suzy, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 24)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 25)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1996 (Box-folder 23 / 26)
  - Hammer Miscellaneous Incoming, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 1)
  - Harms, Jane, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 2)
  - Henke, Russ, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 3)
  - Holsinger, Peggy, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 4)
  - Junso, Pamela, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 5-7)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 8)
  - Lane, Nancy, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 9)
  - Mast, Jane C., 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 10)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 11)
  - Over time/Part-time Schedules, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 12)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual Updates, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 13)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 14)
  - Resident Info sent to Daphne Crosbie, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 15)
  - Residential Services, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 16)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 17)
  - Robson, Sandy, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 18)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 19)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 20)
  - Survey/Questionnaire, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 21)
  - Swap, Pamela, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 22)
  - Taylor, Loretta, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 23)
  - Virts, Rob, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 24)
  - Weekly Schedule, 1996 (Box-folder 24 / 25)
  - Attendance Sheets, 1996 (Box-folder 25 / 1)
  - Austby, Julie, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 1)
  - Barthel, Gerry, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 2)
  - Boehning, Greg, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 3)
  - Contract Professionals, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 4)
  - Degel, Peter (Dr.), 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 5)
  - Department of Public Health and Human Services, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 6)
  - Blouke, Peter S. (Dr.), 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 7)
  - Mathews, Joe, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 8)
  - Dixon, Virgil, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 9)
  - Franklin, Rosella, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 10)
  - Haggerty, Suzy, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 11)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 12)
  - Hammer Miscellaneous Incoming, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 13)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 14)
  - Smoking Issue, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 15)
  - Draft Bills, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 16)
  - Harms, Jane, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 17)
  - Henke, Russ, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 18)
  - Junso, Pamela, 1997 (Box-folder 25 / 19-22)
  - Lane, Nancy, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 1)
  - Martin, Barbara N., 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 2)
  - Massey, Tammy, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 3)
  - Mast, Jane C., 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 4)
  - Montana Development Center (MDC), 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 5)
  - Nephew, Michael, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 6)
  - O’Neil, Rita, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 7)
  - Over time/Part-time Schedule, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 8)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual Updates, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 9)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 10)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 11)
  - Resident Information sent to Daphne Crosbie, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 12)
  - Residential Services, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 13)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 14)
  - Robson, Sandy, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 15)
  - Michael’s P.T and O.T. Info, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 16)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 17)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 18)
  - Virts, Rob, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 19)
  - Weekly Schedule, 1997 (Box-folder 26 / 20)
  - Austby, Julie, 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 21)
  - Contract Professionals, 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 22)
  - Degel, Peter (Dr.), 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 23)
  - Department of Public Health and Human Services (DPHHS) Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 24)
  - Ekanger, Laurie, 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 25)
  - Mathews, Joe, 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 26)
  - Franklin, Rosella, 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 27)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 28)
  - Hammer Miscellaneous Incoming, 1998 (Box-folder 26 / 29)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 1)
  - Harms, Jane, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 2)
  - Henke, Russ, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 3)
  - Medicaid Services, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 4)
  - Junso, Pamela, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 5-8)
  - Lane, Nancy, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 9)
  - Lien, Deanna, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 10)
  - Martin, Barbara N., 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 11)
  - Mast, Jane C., 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 12)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 13)
  - Nephew, Michael, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 14)
  - O’Neil, Rita, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 15)
  - Over time/Part-time Schedules, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 16)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual Updates, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 17)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 18)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 19)
  - Resident Information sent to Daphne Crosbie, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 20)
  - Residential Services Correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 21)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 22)
  - Robson, Sandy, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 23)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 24)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 25)
  - Weekly Schedule, 1998 (Box-folder 27 / 26)
  - Austby, Julie, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 1)
  - Barthel, Gerry, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 2)
  - Boehning, Greg, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 3)
  - Contract Professionals, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 4)
  - Degel, Peter (Dr.), 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 5)
  - Department of Health and Human Services (DPHHS), 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 6)
  - Ekanger, Laurie, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 7)
  - Mathews, Joe, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 8)
  - Flesjer, Lilla, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 9)
  - Franklin, Rosella, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 10)
  - Hammer Miscellaneous Incoming, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 12)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 13)
  - Hammer Staff Memos, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 14)
  - Harms, Jane, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 15)
  - Henke, Russ, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 16)
  - Junso, Pamela, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 17-20)
  - Lane, Nancy, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 21)
  - Lien, Deanna, 1999 (Box-folder 28 / 22)
  - Mast, Jane C., 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 1)
  - Montana Developmental Center (MDC), 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 2)
  - Nephew, Michael, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 3)
  - Over time/Part-time Schedules, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 4)
  - O’Neil, Rita, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 5)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual Updates, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 6)
  - Recreation/Developmental, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 7)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 8)
  - Resident Info sent to Daphne Crosbie, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 9)
  - Residential Services, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 10)
  - Robinson, Michael, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 11)
  - Robson, Sandy, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 12)
  - SIC Notebook Pages, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 13)
  - Surveys/Questionnaires, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 14)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 15)
  - Medicaid Survey, 1999 (Box-folder 29 / 16)
- Subject Files
  - Annual Reports, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 29 / 17)
  - Budget, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 29 / 18-20)
  - Ekanger, Laurie – Director, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 29 / 21-22)
  - Gray, Gail – Director, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 29 / 23-25)
  - Legislative Diaries, 2001 (Box-folder 29 / 26)
  - Melcher Diary, 1999 (Box-folder 30 / 1)
  - MPEA, 1985-1999 (Box-folder 30 / 2)
  - Safeguarding Medication Stored and Administered at DPHHS Facilities, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 30 / 3)
  - Strike Plan, 1981-2003 (Box-folder 30 / 4)
- Meeting Minutes
  - Admissions Committee, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 30 / 5)
  - Agency Management Meetings, 1991-1999 (Box-folder 30 / 6-10)
  - Behavior Management Meetings, 1992 (Box-folder 30 / 11)
  - Bomb Threat Disaster Drill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 30 / 12)
  - Clerical/Fiscal Services Staff Meetings, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 30 / 13-14)
  - Core Mealtime Committee, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 30 / 15)
  - Department Director’s Meetings, 1990 (Box-folder 30 / 16)
  - Departmental Manager’s Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 30 / 17)
  - Developmental Services Staff Meetings, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 30 / 18-19)
  - Disaster Drill Meetings, 1987 (Box-folder 30 / 20)
  - Food Services Staff Meetings, 1986-1999 (Box-folder 30 / 21-22)
  - Habilitation Management Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 30 / 23)
  - Human Rights Committee Meetings, 1984-1998 (Box-folder 30 / 24-26)
  - Infection Control Committee Meetings, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 30 / 27-29)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 30 / 30-35)
  - Program Manager’s Meetings, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 31 / 1)
  - Maintenance/Custodial Staff Meetings, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 31 / 2-3)
  - Management Team Meetings, 1985 (Box-folder 31 / 4)
  - Medical Services Staff Meetings, 1986-1999 (Box-folder 31 / 5-6)
  - Nursing Staff Meetings, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 31 / 7)
  - Quality Assurance Committee Meetings, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 31 / 8-9)
  - Reinforcement Committee Meetings, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 31 / 10)
  - A.M. Residential Services Staff Meeting, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 31 / 11-12)
  - P.M. Residential Services Staff Meeting, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 31 / 13)
  - Night Watch Residential Services Staff Meeting, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 31 / 14-15)
  - Supervisor’s Meetings, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 31 / 16-19)
  - Treatment Services Department Management Team Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 31 / 20)
  - Vocational Training Task Force Meetings, 1990 (Box-folder 31 / 21)
- Scrapbooks and Photo Albums
  - Scrapbooks and Photo Albums, 1960-1980 (Box-folder 32-33)
  - Scrapbooks and Photo Albums, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 34-35)
  - Scrapbooks and Photo Albums, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 36-38)
  - Scrapbooks and Photo Albums, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 39)
  - Slides, 1969-2003 (Box-folder 40)
- Case Files (RESTRICTED)
  - Allard, Esther, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 41 / 1)
  - Allen, Lonnie, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 41 / 2-3)
  - Allmer, William, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 41 / 4)
  - Bigaman, Donna Mae, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 41 / 5)
  - Best, Deborah Lee, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 41 / 6)
  - Brand, Kimberly, 1984-2000 (Box-folder 41 / 7-8)
  - Brown, Luann Marie, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 41 / 9)
  - Carman, Lora Linda, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 41 / 10)
  - Cleeton, James, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 41 / 11-12)
  - Collins, Laura Jane, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 41 / 13)
  - Doggett, William Andrew, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 41 / 14)
  - Easter, Nancy Hayden, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 41 / 15)
  - Elfring, Larry William, 1982-2000 (Box-folder 41 / 16 – 42 / 1)
  - Erickson, Ronald, 1980-2000 (Box-folder 42 / 2-3)
  - Foley, Margaret Rose, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 42 / 4)
  - Fire Moon, Melda, 1981-2003 (Box-folder 42 / 5-7)
  - French, Marlene, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 42 / 8)
  - Gehnert, Ruth Janice, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 42 / 9)
  - Goins, James “Jimmie”, 1991-2003 (Box-folder 42 / 10-11)
  - Gregory, Tom, 1979 (Box-folder 42 / 12)
  - Helgenson, Donald, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 42 / 13)
  - Hollow Horn, Ronald William, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 42 / 14)
  - Huber, Lyle, 1981-2003 (Box-folder 42 / 15 – 43 / 1)
  - Hughett, Paul Terry, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 43 / 2)
  - Hunt, Michael, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 43 / 3-4)
  - Jackson, Diane, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 43 / 5)
  - Jappe, Bill, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 43 / 6)
  - Jung, Pamela, 1984-1998 (Box-folder 43 / 7-8)
  - Krall, Katherine Coleen, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 43 / 9)
  - Krantz, Herman, 1990-2003 (Box-folder 43 / 10 -11)
  - Kinsey, Marlene, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 43 / 12)
  - Lawlor, Rebecca Annette, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 43 / 13)
  - LeDoux, Virginia Delphine, 1980-2000 (Box-folder 43 / 14-15)
  - Lincoln, Mabel Ann, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 44 / 1)
  - Logan, Virginia, 1981-2003 (Box-folder 44 / 2-3)
  - Longee, Russel Thomas, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 44 / 4)
  - McCormick, Mary Pat, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 44 / 5)
  - Meissel, Thomas Lynn, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 44 / 6)
  - Miles, Elsie, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 44 / 7)
  - Mogen, Randall George, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 44 / 8)
  - Morehouse, Beverly Jean, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 44 / 9)
  - Miller, Judy, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 44 / 10-11)
  - Mills, Robert Hawley, 1981 (Box-folder 44 / 12)
  - Ness, Dickson O’Dell, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 44 / 13)
  - Newman, Geraldine, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 44 / 14)
  - Ostwald, Herman, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 44 / 15)
  - Reichert, Carol, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 44 / 16-17)
  - Rones, Steven, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 45 / 1)
  - St. Germain, Isador, 1980-1996 (Box-folder 45 / 2-3)
  - Sather, Michael Anthony, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 45 / 4)
  - Schell, Raymond, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 45 / 5)
  - Seteren, John Lawrence, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 45 / 6)
  - Simons, Candace Larue, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 45 / 7)
  - Skartved, Dean, 1991-2003 (Box-folder 45 / 8-9)
  - Smith, Sandra, 1989-2003 (Box-folder 45 / 10-12)
  - Stearns, Sanford Elmer, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 45 / 13)
  - Weer, Linda Lou, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 46 / 1)
  - Weeres, Merle “Tony”, 1983-1999 (Box-folder 46 / 2-3)
  - Welborn, Bari Lynn, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 46 / 4)
  - Worthem, Betty, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 46 / 5)
  - Wright, Barry, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 46 / 6)